One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The Ruins of Oden Castle
أطلال قلعة أودين
Big Bro!
أخي الكبير
Boss Holdem!
هولديم-ساما
Tama!
تاما
Big Bro!
أخي الكبير
Hold on tight!
تشبثي بي جيدًا
I will!
حاضرة
Alright! Let's run!
حسنًا، لنهرب
Boss Holdem!
هولديم-ساما
No way...! He beat a headliner with one blow?!
أيعقل أنك هُزمت بضربة واحدة رغم أنك من الشينوتشي؟
Who is he?!
من فعل هذا؟
Luffy, you moron! Now you've done it...
لوفي الوغد، لم يجدر به فعل ذلك
Luffytaro!
لوفيتارو-سان
Otama!
أوتاما-تشان
Don't worry! Leave the kid to Luffytaro!
لا تقلقي، دعي أمر الطفلة للوفيتارو
Keep going! We need to reach the town's entrance!
لا تتوقف، انطلق نحو مدخل البلدة
Take back the treasure ship! We can't lose our food!
استعيدوا سفينة المؤن وإلا فقدنا طعامنا
Hold on tight!
تشبثي بي جيدًا
Okay, Big Bro! I won't let go no matter what!
حاضرة يا أخي الكبير، لن أفلتك حتمًا
B-Big Bro...
...أ-أخي الكبير
Slice him up!
مزقوه
Outta the way!
ابتعد عن طريقي
I've gotta catch up to Zoro before they eat all the good stuff!
علينا اللحاق بزورو بسرعة قبل أن يأكل كل تلك الأطعمة الشهية
That's perfect! Let's hitch a ride! I'm gonna jump!
رائع، سأمتطي ذلك الحصان وننطلق
Who's there?!
من هذا؟
Who's holding me in his arms?!
من الذي يحتضنني فجأة؟
Giddyup, horse!
تقدم أيها الحصان
Wait, what're you doing?!
ماذا تفعل يا هذا؟
– What?! She's a human?!
ماذا؟ بشرية؟
No, she's a horse!
كلا، بل حصان
How dare you get on Madam Speed like that?!
كيف تجرؤ على امتطاء سبيد-ساما؟
Yank them down!
أسقطيهما
Get off of me, you jackasses!
ابتعد عني أيها الوغد
Hey, Tama, make a dumpling!
تاما، أعطني إحدى الدانغو
Just do it!
هيا بسرعة
Millet Dumpling!
كيبي دانغو
Now, tame the horse!
عظيم، روّضي الحصان
What? That's impossible! It doesn't work on humans!
محال، قدرتي ليست فعّالة على البشر
You don't know until you try!
لن نعرف ما لم نحاول
That looks delicious!
تبدو لذيذة
Where would you like to go, Master?!
إلى أين تريدين الذهاب يا سيدتي؟
You did it!
مرحى
It worked!
لقد نفعت
But... why?
ولكن لماذا؟
She's half-horse, isn't she?
ربما لأنها نصف حصان؟
Madam Speed...
...سـ-سبيد-ساما
After her!
الحقوا بها
She's too fast!
يا لسرعتها
Alright, Horsella! Follow that treasure ship!
حسنًا يا أومامي، الحقي بسفينة الطعام
I'm not your servant!
أنا لستُ خادمتك
My name is Speed! Don't call me Horsella like we're friends or something!
اسمي سبيد، لا تنادني أومامي كأنك تعرفني
I want you to do as Big Bro says, Horsella.
نفذي ما قاله أخي الكبير يا أومامي-تشان
Of course, Master!
مفهوم يا سيدتي
I can't believe a headliner like Speed is obeying them!
لا أصدق أنّ الشينوتشي سبيد-ساما خضعت لهما بسهولة
Do they have some kind of dirt on her?
أفعلوا شيئًا بها؟
Big Bro...
...أخي الكبير
Red Hawk!
الصقر الأحمر ريد هوك
Fire Fist!
قبضة النار هيكين
Big Bro... Back there...
...أخي الكبير، قبل قليل
you were just like Ace.
بدوت مثل أيس
Did you say something?
أقلتِ شيئًا؟
No!
لا
Never mind.
لم أقل شيئًا
Your life is mine.
أنا من سيسلب حياتك
What'd you say?!
ماذا قلت؟
Take him out!
لنقضِ عليه
– Yeah!
أجل
Room!
غرفة روم
That ability...
...تلك القدرة
Those tattoos...
...وذلك الوشم
Is he...?!
...أيعقل أنه
He could be!
احتمالٌ وارد
They did have an alliance!
فقد شكّلا تحالفًا
Roronoa is with that group but at least he knows the plan.
رورونوا-يا معه وهو يعرف خطتنا حق المعرفة
He surely wouldn't do anything stupid like taking down Holdem.
مهما تهورا، فلن يرتكبا حماقةً كالإطاحة بهولديم
Boss Holdem!
هولديم-ساما
If they were to do something to him...
إن ألحقوا به أي أذى
that would be it...
...فخطتنا
for our plan...
ستفشل
Get lost, Hawkins!
اختفِ يا هوكينز
Shambles!
فوضى شامبلز
Help me!
ساعدوني
Wait?! How am I alive?!
ماذا؟ أأنا حي؟
What the hell?! His lower body's moving by itself!
ما هذا؟ جزءه السفلي يتحرك بنفسه
Just... what kind of ability was that?
ما القدرة التي استخدمها قبل قليل؟
Straw Sword!
سيف القش وارا بيديتو
Take off your mask...
اخلع قناعك
Trafalgar Law!
يا ترافلغار لاو
I knew it wasn't gonna be that easy, Basil Hawkins!
توقعتُ أنك لن تكون خصمًا سهلًا يا باسيل هوكينز
But...
...ولكن
Blah, blah, blah! Time to shut you up!
كفاك ثرثرة وإلا قطعت لسانك
Get him!
عليكم به
Wait!
انتظروا
Amputate!
بتر أمبتيتو
Takt!
إيقاع تاكت
Shambles!
فوضى شامبلز
You cut up all my proxies.
شطرت كل أتباعي
You certainly adapt quickly.
واستنتجت ماهية قدرتي بسرعة
I was just bluffing.
لكنه مجرد تهديد
Murder isn't my style. I am a doctor, after all.
بصفتي طبيبًا، لا أفضّل القتل
Welcome to Wano. It's been some time since that fateful day at Sabaody.
أهلًا بك في بلاد وانو، لم أرك منذ اليوم المصيري في أرخبيل شابوندي
Since your allies are here too, I'm assuming you're not here as a tourist.
لا يبدو أنك أتيت لتلهو، فحلفاءك هنا أيضًا
You thought I didn't know?
أتوقعت أنني لا أعرف بشأنهم؟
I've already crossed paths with Straw Hat's group.
التقيتُ بقبعة القش ومن معه مسبقًا
If you were looking to silence me, I'm afraid it's too late.
لا بدّ أنك أردت قتلي قبل انتشار خبر وجودكم هنا
The thieves fled after defeating Boss Holdem!
ثمة لصوص أطاحوا بهولديم-ساما ولاذوا بالفرار
We've already informed Master Jack!
لقد أبلغنا جاك-ساما بذلك
They beat Holdem and now Jack has been notified?
أطاحوا بهولديم ووصل الخبر إلى جاك؟
As you just heard, your efforts were in vain.
كما سمعت تمامًا، ذهبت جهودك أدراج الرياح
And of course, this means Captain Kaido will become aware of these goings on.
وبالطبع، سيعرف كايدو-سان عما تفعله أنت وطاقم قبعة القش هنا
Those morons! This is the worst-case scenario!
بسببهما، سنواجه أسوأ الاحتمالات الممكنة
Hey, you guys! Get out the way!
أفسحا الطريق
Roronoa?!
رورونوا-يا؟
Excuse us! We need to pass! We're in a hurry!
أفسحا الطريق رجاءً، إننا في عجلة من أمرنا
Get them! They stole our food!
الحقوهم، لقد سرقوا طعامنا
Roronoa!
رورونوا-يا
Oh, Traffy.
مرحبًا يا تراو
You idiot!
أيها الوغد
Is there a problem, Traffy?
ما الأمر يا تراو؟
Screw you!
...أيها الوغد
What?! Who is that?!
ماذا؟ من ذلك؟
Not only did you become a fugitive, you drew Jack's attention!
كشفت أمرنا عند جاك، ناهيك عن وضعك في قائمة المطلوبين مسبقًا
You promised that you were gonna stay out of trouble!
ألم تعدني بعدم إثارة الجلبة ولفت الأنظار؟
My bad.
أعتذر
Also...
...وأيضًا
why are you even in Kuri?!
لماذا أتيت إلى مقاطعة كوري؟
You were supposed to pose as a ronin in the Flower Capital!
يُفترض أن تكون رونين في عاصمة الزهور
They know each other?
هل يعرفان بعضهما؟
Is everything okay?
هل الأمور على ما يرام؟
No, it's not!
كلا
I'm sorry!
اعذرني
I had no choice!
لم يكن أمامي خيارٌ آخر
I ran into Luffy.
فقد قابلت لوفي صدفةً
Straw Hat! It's always him!
قبعة القش-يا، هو مجددًا؟
Zorojuro! We're leaving town!
زوروجورو-سان، سنخرج من البلدة
Alright...
عظيم
Let's unload at Okobore Town!
لنفرغ الحمولة في بلدة أوكوبوري
Mom! I'm hungry!
أمي، أنا جائع
You have to endure it.
اصمد قليلًا
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Th-That's...
...إ-إنها
a treasure ship!
سفينة مؤن
There are so many fish!
ثمة كثير من الأسماك
Food! There's food!
طعام، طعام
A treasure ship is here!
وصلت سفينة مؤن
We're saved!
لن نموت جوعًا
Amazing!
مذهل
Hurry, everyone!
أسرعوا يا رفاق
It's food!
إنه طعام
Can we have it?!
أيمكننا أكله؟
Thank goodness!
شكرًا لكم
We can survive!
لقد أنقذتم حياتنا
It's delicious!
لذيذة
There's so much food!
ثمة كمية هائلة من الطعام
We won't starve! This is so great!
لن نتضور جوعًا بعد الآن، شكرًا لكم
What a relief...
...هذا مطمئن
Whoa-whoa-whoa, wait!
كلا، كلا، انتظروا
Those aren't leftovers yet!
لم نرسل إليكم بقايا طعامنا بعد
Stay away from the treasure ship!
ابتعدوا عن سفينة المؤن
You trash!
يا حثالة البشر
You shouldn't even be touching that food!
لا يحق لكم لمس هذا الطعام
You idiots forgot your place!
يبدو أنكم نسيتم مكانتكم
We won't let you pass!
سنقف لكم بالمرصاد
So you're siding with the trash!
أنتم تناصرون حثالة الشعب
This is coming out of your hides, you fools!
ستدفعون ثمن فعلتكم أيها الأوغاد
Sorry to keep you waiting!
معذرةً على التأخير
It's water!
إنه ماء
It won't poison you! Help yourselves!
إنه غير مسموم، اشربوا منه
It's been years since we've had this much drinking water!
لم نحظَ بهذا القدر من المياه العذبة منذ سنوات
Thank goodness! Thank goodness!
شكرًا لكم، شكرًا لكم
I'm Luffytaro, in case anyone comes and asks!
أنا لوفيتارو، إن سألكم أحد من أين لكم هذا فأخبروه باسمي
Thank you, Luffytaro!
شكرًا لك يا لوفيتارو-سان
Big Bro!
أخي الكبير
Tama!
تاما
Traffy!
تراو
It's good to see you!
لم أرك منذ مدة
Straw Hat...
قبعة القش-يا
in Wano, this is considered an insurrection.
ما تفعله يعد تمردًا ضد بلاد وانو
An insurrection? This is nothing like that!
تمرد؟ الأمر ليس كذلك
Here!
خذي
It's an apple!
تفاحة
Tama...
تاما
I'm paying you back for feeding me.
ها أنا أرد معروف إطعامك إياي سابقًا
This is just the start!
وما هذه إلا البداية فحسب
Look at all this meat!
انظروا إلى هذا اللحم
Hey! Guys!
مهلًا يا رفاق
Save some meat for me!
أبقوا بعضًا من اللحم لي
Meat! Meat, meat!
لحم، لحم، لحم
Meat, meat, meat, meat!
لحم، لحم، لحم، لحم
Meat!
لحم
Boss Holdem!
هولديم-ساما
The fire is spreading!
النار تنتشر بسرعة
Where are the firefighters?!
أين فرقة الإطفاء؟
Boss Holdem! Stay with us!
هولديم-ساما، تماسك
Please wake up!
استيقظ رجاءً
Only the lion woke up! That's scary!
استيقظ الأسد وحده، مخيف
That's right...
هذا صحيح
It's Monkey D. Luffy, Roronoa Zoro,
مونكي دي لوفي ورورونوا زورو
and Trafalgar Law.
وترافلغار لاو
I don't want to sell myself short...
لا أقصد التقليل من نفسي
but when the foe is as troublesome as these three, it's too much even for me.
ولكن باجتماع أولئك الثلاثة، لن أقوى على التصدي لهم وحدي
It's so delicious!
لذيذة
Good for you, Tama!
سعيد من أجلك يا تاما
Y-Yes!
أ-أجل
I don't know if I could ever top a wonderful birthday like this!
هذا أسعد يوم ميلاد في حياتي
Tama!
تاما
Don't set the bar too low!
لا تستكثري شيئًا بسيطًا كهذا
I'm gonna make this normal for you!
سأجعل شعورك هذا يتكرر كل يوم
Before we leave this country,
حالما نغادر هذه البلاد
I'll make it a place where you can eat as much as you want!
ستكون بلاد لا تعانين فيها من الجوع أبدًا
When we come back to this country...
حينما نعود إلى هذه البلاد
Hm? You don't want that?
ألن يسعدك ذلك؟
O-Of course...
بـ-بلى
Of course, and it makes me happy!
سأكون سعيدةً بالطبع
It just surprised me a bit...!
أنا فقط متفاجئة
I see!
هكذا إذًا
Man! You've really gone and done it!
بحق، لقد تهورت مجددًا
Now, they'll really come after us! Stay on your guard!
سيسعون خلفنا حقًّا هذه المرة، استعد لهذا
Like you can talk!
أنت من أثار الجلبة هنا
We shouldn't stick around here. Time to go!
لا يجدر بنا المكوث هنا طويلًا، لنرحل
Follow me!
اتبعوني
We'll go to the ruins of Oden Castle at the top of that mountain!
سنذهب إلى أطلال قلعة أودين القابعة في قمة الجبل
Okay, I'm heading off too!
حسنًا، سأرحل أيضًا
Thank you!
شكرًا لك
Alright, take good care of her, Horsella!
حسنًا، أعتمد عليك في حمايتها يا أومامي
I am Speed, a headliner of the Beast Pirates!
اسمي سبيد، وأنا أحد شينوتشي قراصنة الوحوش
I don't take orders from you, fool!
لا أتلقى الأوامر منك أيها الوغد
Servants naturally protect their masters!
من البديهي أن يحمي الخدم أسيادهم
Why is a headliner obeying that kid?
لماذا تلك الشينوتشي خاضعة لهذه الطفلة؟
Big Bro...
أخي الكبير
Hm? What is it?
ما الأمر؟
I'll never forget...
أنا لن أنسى
I'll never ever forget the taste of the oshiruko soup and the apple that I had today!
لن أنسى مذاق حساء الأوشيروكو وهذه التفاحة ما حييت
Great!
أجل
When I return to Amigasa Village, I'm gonna give this apple to my master!
سأقدّم هذه التفاحة إلى معلمي حين أصل إلى قرية آميغاسا
Say hi to Grandpa Nose for me! I promise I'll bring back the dog!
بلغي العجوز ذا الأنف تحياتي، سأعيد الكلب لاحقًا بكل تأكيد
I will!
حاضرة
Komachiyo!
كوماتشيو
I want you to help Big Bro!
ساعد أخي الكبير بكل ما أوتيت من قوة
Oh, yeah!
...بالمناسبة
Let me borrow this sword for a little longer! Without it, I can't call myself a samurai!
سأحتفظ بهذا السيف لوقتٍ أطول، فليس بوسعي تمثيل دور الساموراي دونه
You're not even using it!
أنت لا تستخدم هذا السيف أصلًا
Seriously, just let me take a look at it!
دعني أتفحصه قليلًا، جديًّا
I'll let my master know!
سأخبر معلمي بذلك
Yeah, thanks!
أجل، أعتمد عليكِ
We must get going, Master!
علينا أن نغادر يا سيدتي
Oh, thank you!
أجل، شكرًا لك
Have a safe journey!
توخّي الحذر
Okay! Well then...!
حاضرة، مع السلامة
See you around!
إلى اللقاء
Tama!
يا تاما
All right...
...والآن
Luffy!
لوفي
Time to get going!
علينا أن نغادر أيضًا
Mr. Luffytaro!
لوفيتارو-سان
I've never seen this much food before!
لم أرَ هذا الكم من الطعام في حياتي
My grandfather is better!
تحسنت صحة جدي بفضلك
I lived to see this dream come true!
تحقق حلم حياتي
Our child is healthy again!
استعاد طفلنا حيويته
I've never eaten this much before!
لم آكل هذا القدر من الطعام يومًا
That's good!
هذا جيد
All right, then!
حسنًا، وداعًا
– Thank you for the treasure ship!
شكرًا على سفينة المؤن
– Thank you!
شكرًا جزيلًا لكم
– Come visit again!
زورونا مجددًا
Pirates shouldn't be such do-gooders.
العمل الصالح ليس من شيم القراصنة
It makes me sick!
أشعر بالاشمئزاز
That was a nice thing we did!
لقد أحسنّا إليهم
It's still theft.
منذ متى كان الإحسان بالسرقة؟
Guys!
يا رفاق
Take care of yourselves!
اعتنوا بأنفسكم
You didn't become her servant by eating that dumpling, huh?
يبدو أنك لم تصبح خادمها لأنك أكلت الدانغو، بل بمحض إرادتك
So...
أنتِ
why are you coming with us?
لماذا أتيتِ معنا؟
I-I'm sorry! I've always wanted to visit Oden Castle!
أعتذر، طالما أردتُ زيارة قلعة أودين
I will head home right after, so I will not be a burden.
سأعود إلى المنزل حالما نصل إلى هناك لئلا أتسبب لكم بالمتاعب
Should I be worried?
هل أنت موافق؟
Nah!
أجل
Kiku's a good, strong person, so it's gonna be fine!
كيكو فتاة لطيفة وقوية، فما المانع؟
Actually...
كلا
she's hiding something!
بل غامضة وتخفي سرًّا
Hey, Traffy, why are we going to the castle?
بالمناسبة يا تراو، لماذا نذهب إلى القلعة؟
It's not a castle anymore...
لم تعد قلعةً الآن
Only the deserted ruins remain.
لم يتبقّ منها سوى حكام مهجور
Why does he wanna go to Oden Castle?
لماذا يريد الذهاب إلى قلعة أودين؟
Luffytaro and his allies are good people...
لوفيتارو-سان والآخرين أثبتوا طيبتهم
but I can't drop my guard yet.
ولكن ما زال عليّ الحذر منهم
Since we last saw you...
بعد انفصالنا عنكم
we made a plan and set about following it...
وضعنا خطة وكنا نتحرك وفقًا لها
You'll see once you get there.
على أي حال، سترى عندما نصل
First...
أولًا
you're going to meet the ghosts of Wano.
سنلتقي بأشباح بلاد وانو
Ghosts?
أشباح؟
Get ready for a shock...
ستُصدم عند رؤيتهم
Yeah... I was stunned, too.
أجل، صُعقت حين رأيتهم أيضًا
There, you'll learn...
...أنت على وشك
Retainer Kanjuro Grave of...
قبر الخادم كنجورو
Retainer Raizo
قبر الخادم رايزو
Retainer Kin'emon
قبر الخادم كينيمون
Kozuki Momonosuke
قبر كوزكي مومونوسكي
an unbelievable truth!
رؤية حقيقة لا يقبلها عقلك
Kozuki Oden
قبر كوزكي أودين
Anyway...
في كل الأحوال
we can continue this conversation once we reach the ruins of Oden Castle at the summit.
سنتحدث حالما نصل إلى قمة الجبل حيث يقع أطلال قلعة أودين
There's a threat.
ثمة شيءٌ قوي خلفنا
Yeah.
أجل
Maybe it's one of Orochi's assassins.
قد يكون أحد أتباع أوروتشي
Luffy, you go on ahead.
لوفي، اسبقني
I'll catch up to you after I take care of this.
سألحق بك حالما أتولى أمره
Thanks.
أعتمد عليك
I can feel your bloodlust.
أتظن نفسك مختبئًا هكذا؟
There's no castle here!
لا يوجد قلعة
I did say "ruins."
"لهذا قلتُ "أطلال
Ruins of Oden Castle Kuri, Wano
أطلال قلعة أودين مقاطعة كوري في وانو
Oh, yeah.
فهمت
It's this way. Follow me.
من هنا، اتبعاني
What? Hey, Kiku!
مهلًا يا كيكو
What's wrong with her?
ما بالها؟
This place is creepy.
يا له من مكانٍ موحش
It's been abandoned for twenty years.
لأنه مهجور منذ عشرين سنة
What are those?
ما ذلك؟
"Kozuki Oden..."?
"كوزكي أودين"
Look at the other graves, too.
انظر إلى القبور الأخرى أيضًا
"Kozuki..."
كوزكي"
Mo-
مومو
mo-
نو
no-
سكي
Momonosuke is...
مومونوسكي"؟
You know the kid that grave belongs to.
إنه قبر ذلك الطفل الذي تعرفه
It's not just him.
ليس ذلك الطفل فحسب
"Raizo"?!
رايزو؟
"Kanjuro"?!
كنجورو؟
"Kin'emon"?!
كينيمون؟
Why are their graves here?!
لماذا قبورهم هنا؟
Wait a minute, when we were making our way to Wano...
...تذكرت، في طريقنا إلى وانو
I couldn't get in touch with Kin'emon...
لم أستطع التواصل مع كينيمون
Kin'emon
كينيمون
D-Don't tell me...
...أ-أيعقل أنهم
he's dead!
ماتوا؟
Okay, time to head back.
والآن، حان وقت العودة
Where did they go?
أين ذهبوا؟
It's a dock.
إنه مرسى
No way...
محال
They can't be dead!
يستحيل أن يموتوا
I thought Kin'emon was waiting here...
ظننت أنّ كينيمون ينتظرنا هنا
Grave of Kin'emon
قبر كينيمون
He's been gone for quite a while.
لقد اختفى منذ فترة طويلة
Gone?!
اختفى؟
He might emerge at night.
قد يخرج ليلًا
He showed up repeated last night.
فقد ظهر مرارًا وتكرارًا الليلة الماضية
That sounds like he's a ghost or something!
لِمَ تتحدث عنه وكأنه شبح؟
What's up with these graves?! Spit it out, Traffy!
ما قصة هذه القبور؟ أخبرني يا تراو
Is there something you don't wanna say?!
أثمة شيء لا تريد إخباري به؟
I'm not the one who should be telling you about it.
لستُ من يجدر به إخبارك عن هذا الأمر
Sir Luffy!
...لوفي-دونو
Kin!
كين
I'm glad that you're alive!
يسعدني أنك على قيد الحياة
I'm sorry that I couldn't come to get you...
المعذرة، لم أستطع التواصل معك
It's so great that you arrived safely.
الأهم أنكم وصلتم بخير وسلام
I'm afraid I have a bad case of the runs.
خشيت أن يستمر الإسهال الحاد
I thought I'd be confined to the outhouse again tonight.
ولا أخرج من المرحاض الليلة مجددًا
But I'm starting to feel a little better.
ولكنني أشعر بتحسن الآن
"Foxfire" Kin'emon Retainer of the Kozuki Clan
ثعلب النار كينيمون خادم عشيرة الكوزكي
Well, at any rate, it was pretty bad.
حسنًا، كان الإسهال مؤلمًا
He's alive, Traffy!
إنه حي يا تراو
When did I say he wasn't?
متى قلت أنه مات؟
I meant he might emerge from the bathroom tonight.
كنتُ أقصد أنه سيخرج من الحمام ليلًا
That was misleading!
أنت تتلاعب بي
Sir Kin!
كين-ساما
Kiku!
كيكو
You're back!
سعيدةٌ لعودتك
I really missed you!
اشتقت إليك، اشتقت إليك
I was so uneasy!
وددت رؤيتك بشدة
Honestly! If you were back, why didn't you come tell me?!
بحقك، لماذا لم تخبرني بأنك عدت؟
I was worried about you. How cold of you!
كنت قلقة عليك، يا لقسوتك
I-I'm sorry!
أ-أعتذر
Lord Momonosuke is okay, too?
هل مومونوسكي-ساما بخير أيضًا؟
Yes.
أجل
Momo's alive, too, huh?
مومو حي أيضًا؟
Wait, Kiku and Kin know each other?
ماذا؟ هل كيكو وكين يعرفان بعضهما؟
Seems like they're very close.
تبدو علاقتهما وطيدة
What?
كيكو، كيف تعرفين لوفي-دونو والآخرين؟
What?! Are these the ones who...?!
...ماذا؟ أيعقل أنّ هؤلاء
I don't know who to tell what first...!
لا أعلم ماذا أقول أو من أين أبدأ
But you are correct, Kiku!
أصبتِ يا كيكو
They are strong allies that are going to help us take down Orochi!
إنهم حلفاؤنا الأقوياء، وقد أتوا لمساعدتنا على هزيمة أوروتشي
Sir Luffy and Sir Law!
لوفي-دونو ولاو-دونو
Hey, Luffy!
يا لوفي
You arrived safely!
وصلت بسلام إذًا
Lord Momonosuke?!
مومونوسكي-ساما
Luffy, I was just practicing my swordsmanship!
لوفي، كنت أتدرب على المبارزة
Good!
هكذا إذًا
Watch this!
انظر
Lord Momonosuke, I'm glad that you're okay!
مومونوسكي-ساما، يسعدني أنك بخير
Is Dog Pops here in Wano, too, Momo?
هل الكلب العجوز موجود في وانو أيضًا يا مومو؟
What? Momo?!
ماذا؟ مومو؟
It's rude to address Lord Momonosuke so casually!
من الوقاحة التحدث إلى مومونوسكي-ساما دون لقب التشريف
Oh, it's fine, Kiku.
لا بأس يا كيكو
What? Okay.
حاضرة
Of course, Inuarashi is here, too.
بالطبع، إينواراشي موجود هنا أيضًا
So he is!
فهمت
So that just leaves the others now.
لم يتبقّ سواهم إذًا
Are we there yet? We've been walking for ages.
ألم نصل بعد؟ تعبت من المشي
He said to look for the castle ruins, so it has to be on this mountain.
أخبرنا أن نبحث عن أطلال قلعة لذا لا شك أنّ هذا الجبل هو المقصود
I'm glad that we finally got in touch with him!
من الجيد أننا تواصلنا معه
Luffy, there you are!
أتيت يا لوفي
– Luffy!
لوفي
Guys! Over here!
يا رفاق، تعالوا
I'm glad that you're okay!
يسعدني أنك بخير
Garchu!
غارتشو
Luffy! You're dressed like a samurai! That's so cool!
لوفي، تبدو ملابس الساموراي رائعة عليك
What took you guys so long?!
لماذا تأخرتم يا رفاق؟
We even searched the seabed for you!
لأننا كنا نبحث عنك في كل مكان
We found your vivre card, so we knew you were alive, at least.
علمنا أنك حي بفضل عثورنا على الفيفر كارد خاصتك
Onami!
أونامي
Momo!
مومو-تشان
Kin'emon, how are you doing?
كينيمون-سان، كيف حالك الآن؟
I'm getting by.
تحسنت قليلًا
Momonosuke, you look good.
مومونوسكي-سان، تبدو بأفضل حال
I thought so, you dirty brat!
أنت شقي منحرف كما توقعت
So you've returned to the crew, Sir Sanji.
يبدو أنك عدت إلى الطاقم يا سانجي-دونو
Yeah, sorry to make you worry.
أجل، أعتذر على إقلاقك
Kin!
كين-سان
Are these some of Luffytaro's friends?
أهؤلاء رفاق لوفيتارو-سان؟
What a lovely lady!
يا لجمالها من آنسة
Hey!
مهلًا
That's enough! Get off of her!
هذا يكفي، ابتعد عنها
You're being insolent, Bonekichi!
أنت تزعجني أيها العظمي-كيتشي
Leave him alone, Brook!
دعه وشأنه يا بروك
Right, Momo?
صحيح يا مومو-تشان؟
Onami...
أونامي
Momo!
مومو
These are indeed Sir Luffy's friends.
جميعهم رفاق لوفي-دونو
The people we will rely on!
إنهم أشخاص جديرين بالثقة
Lord Momonosuke, I'm glad you're able to smile again.
مومونوسكي-ساما، سعيدةٌ برؤيتك بأفضل حال
Captain!
قبطان
Oh, you guys.
أهلًا يا رفاق
How's Bepo doing?
كيف حال بيبو؟
He hasn't come out of the bush yet. He's still got the runs.
لا يزال في الغابة بسبب الإسهال
What's wrong with everyone?
ما خطب الجميع؟
Straw Hat.
قبعة القش-يا
Let's talk inside.
لنتحدث في الداخل
Okay.
حسنًا
We stole safe food from the farm.
لقد سرقنا طعامًا صالحًا للأكل من المزرعة
So you're the one who did it!
إذًا فأنتم السارقون الذين كانوا يتحدثون عنهم
This ruined castle will be our headquarters.
ستكون هذه القلعة المدمرة مقرنا الرئيس
What a messy room!
يا لها من حجرة مهترأة
I'm sorry, everyone...
سامحوني جميعكم
Sir Luffy! Everyone!
لوفي-دونو والبقية دون استثناء
Thank you for coming to Wano!
شكرًا لمجيئكم إلى بلاد وانو
As ever, I am extremely grateful!
يعجز لساني عن شكركم حقًّا
Don't mention it!
لا داعي للشكر
Yeah!
أجل
First things first, there is a secret we haven't told you about...
أولًا، بالإضافة إلى هوية مومونوسكي-ساما الحقيقية
aside from Lord Momonosuke's true identity.
ثمة أمر آخر لم أخبركم به بعد
You guys have so many secrets!
متى تنتهي أسراركم يا رفاق؟
Just tell us everything already! You can trust us!
أخبرنا بكل شيء حالًا، فنحن لسنا غرباء
He's right.
هذا صحيح
We're friends!
ألسنا أصحاب؟
You're absolutely right. I'm sorry!
أجل معكم حق، المعذرة
It's just that you're not going to believe what I'm about to say.
لكنكم لن تصدقوا ما سأخبركم به
What is it? Just say it!
ما هو؟ هيا أخبرنا
You know Kanjuro and Raizo.
أنتم تعرفون كنجورو ورايزو
And the three of us here.
ونحن الثلاثة الماثلين أمام أعينكم
The five of us...
...نحن الخمسة
are really...
...في حقيقة الأمر
from the past!
أتينا من الماضي
The past...?
الماضي؟
What do you mean by that?
ما الذي تقصده؟
Retainer Kanjuro Retainer Raizo Kozuki Oden Retainer Kin'emon Kozuki Momonosuke Grave of...
قبر كوزكي أودين قبر الخادم كينيمون قبر كوزكي مومونوسكي قبر الخادم كنجورو قبر الخادم رايزو
Kin'emon
كينيمون
Kanjuro
كنجورو
Raizo
رايزو
Momonosuke
مومونوسكي
The thing is, we are from a Wano twenty years in the past...
الحقيقة أننا أتينا من بلاد وانو القائمة قبل عشرين سنة
verily crossing through time to the present day.
سافرنا عبر الزمن إلى بلاد وانو الحاضرة
Huh?!
ماذا؟